flyvpn.com 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy - FlyVPN

Scope of Privacy Policy

This policy applies to how we handle personal identification information that you provide to us when you log on to our website and servers.

Collection and Use of Information

We will collect, store, and use the following personal information about you to provide you with our VPN services:  
1.Information with which you provide us during the creation of a VPN account, such as the name, phone number, and e-mail address;  
2.Information about your network ISP, information provided by your browser, your current IP address and GPS address, and the language, version and identification number of the device you.

We may use your information for the following purposes:  
1.Perform authentication during your use (or trial) of our services;  
2.Offer customer services, provide security protection, detect fraud, archive data, and perform backup while providing VPN services;<  
3.Help us develop new services and improve existing service experience.

Disclosure and Sharing of Information

We will not lease or sell your personal identification information to anyone except for the following circumstances:  
1.You agree to allow a third party to share your information.  
2.We have to share your information as requested by court summons, legal orders, or legal procedures.  
3.You violate the terms of service or provisions for the use of services.

Cookie

Our webpage will set or access cookies associated with our website on your computer for website login. Other companies are not allowed to access cookies that we have set and have to follow their own privacy policies.

Security Assurance

This website respects your information and privacy. Your account is password protected to ensure that your privacy and information are secure. Wherever possible, our website will use the SSL encryption protocol in line with universal standards to ensure secure data transmission. This website is committed to complying with internationally recognized privacy guidelines for the protection of personal information while abiding by legal requirements, even beyond the requirements of these guidelines. The website will ensure that its staff comply with the most stringent security and confidentiality rules. In view of the special nature of the Internet, the website cannot guarantee that our data transmission is 100% reliable. The website will take all practicable measures to ensure that any information collected by us is not interfered by third parties and store data in accordance with our established stringent security and confidentiality rules.

Changes to Privacy Policy

We will make changes to our privacy policy at times. Should there be any major change to the policy regarding the use of users' personal information, we will post relevant provisions at a prominent location on the webpage to notify you of the change in a timely manner.

Questions and Suggestions

If you have any other questions or suggestions, please let us know.

Company Information

Vistra Corporate Services Centre, Wickhams Cay II, Road Town, Tortola, VG1110, British Virgin Islands  
TEL.00852 3008 5679

2017-02-13  
FlyVPN
